Guide to the Charles Frederick Park Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Additional Papers, Accession ARCH-1989-262
  - General Correspondence
    - C.L. Sainsbury (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Society of Economic Geologists (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Stanford University (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - _______ (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - _______, Earth Sciences (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - _______, Earth Sciences (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - State Board of Registration for Geologists and Geophysicists (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - T (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Universities (misc.) (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - University of Arizona (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - University of California-Davis (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - University of Georgia (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - University of North Dakota (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - University of Sydney (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Universidad/Pontificia (Peru) (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - W (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Ken Williams (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Z (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Professional Papers
    - Stock Options Committee (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - _______ (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - _______ (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - _______ (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - _______ (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - _______ (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - _______ (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Consulting (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - _______ (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - _______ (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - _______ (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - _______ (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Consulting (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - _______ (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - _______ (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Consulting (Golden Cycle Coporation) (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - _______ (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - _______ (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - _______ (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - _______ (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - _______ (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - _______ (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - _______ (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - _______ (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - _______ (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - _______ (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - _______ (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - _______ (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - _______ (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - _______ (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - _______ (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Consulting (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - _______ (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - _______ (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - _______ (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - _______ (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - _______ (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - _______ (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - _______ (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - _______ (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - _______ (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - _______ (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - _______ (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - _______ (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - _______ (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Proofs and Revisions of Texts on Ores by Charles Park
    - Blue Binder #1 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Blue Binder #2a (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Blue Binder #2b (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Blue Binder #3a (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Blue Binder #3b (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Blue Binder #3c (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Blue Binder #4a (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Blue Binder #4b (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Green Binder #1 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Green Binder #2 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Homestake Mining Company
    - Homestake Mining Company (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Homestake Mining Company (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Homestake Mining Company: Seventeen bound reports (1965-1975) (Box 7)